how can you add captions like the ones
that you see below this video first of
all let me tell you why you need
captions in your videos let's take
instagram for example when you scroll
down your news feed most of the videos
that you will see they're muted and many
times you are in situations where you
can't turn on your audio you can just
watch it without listening to the video
and this happens more than you think
so if you add captions there someone can
watch it your video without listening to
it and understanding what you're talking
about so what is this tool that i use to
create automated captions below my
videos this tool is called autocad it's
a really smart app on your phone because
i automatically understand what you're
saying and even in my case with my not
perfect english autocad can understand
what i'm saying and you can tweak little
mistakes that could be here and there
don't forget to highlight the keywords
in what you say because this will make
your message even more powerful